cloudwork.com 2015-03-18

# Privacy Policy - CloudWork

This Privacy Policy describes how we treat the information we collect and use when you visit and use the CloudWork website located at cloudwork.com (the "Site") and the services offered by CloudWork (the "Service"). Please read this Privacy Policy to learn more about the ways in which CloudWork protects the privacy of all the users (“User” or “Users”) of the Site and Service .

By using the Service you acknowledge and explicitly agree to be bound by the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy and provide full consent to the collection, storage and processing of your personal data by CloudWork.

If you do not agree to the terms, please do not use the Service or access our Site. The CloudWork Service is not intended for use by children. If you are under 18, you may use the Service only with involvement of a parent or guardian.

Please note that any information you provide to other Site and Service Users or to third parties you may contact through the Site and Service will be collected and used by those parties according to their own terms and privacy policies. CloudWork cannot guarantee that these parties comply with the requirements set forth in data protection legislation.

## Personal Data Collection

When you register we ask for information like your name and email address. We store this information in order to provide you with access to the service and to provide personalized integration services. CloudWork does not collect or store any credit card information. Any credit card information is powered securely by our payment gateway, Ogone Payment Services, a level-1 PCI DSS compliant provider of online payment and risk management services

The User guarantees that the personal information provided is true, accurate and up to date in the manner that reflects the User’s current situation. The User hereby acknowledges that he/she is exclusively responsible for any inaccuracy, falsity, mistake or error in any submitted personal data and information and may be held liable for any damages whatsoever caused to CloudWork or third parties, by virtue of using the CloudWork Service.

CloudWork will also process other technical information relating to your use of the Site, such as accessed web pages and Site areas and IP addresses.

It is not recommended to submit any personal data that is non-professional contact data or which contains sensitive data that is relative to identifiable persons such as:

  * Non-professional contact data such as personal phone numbers or email or home addresses;
  * User’s and or third party’s racial origin, membership in a trade union, religion, ideology and sexual life;
  * User’s and or third party’s health, unless it proves necessary in order to assert any handicap or disability situation for labor purposes; or
  * User’s and or third party’s relative to the commission of criminal offences or proceedings and associated penalties or fines.

## Purposes in Automatic Data Collection and Processing

The data we collect is processed for the purposes indicated in our Terms of Use. Beyond the personal information your are giving us to register for an account, CloudWork will gather some generic information automatically. This information may include the IP address or cookie information assigned to your computer, the number and frequency of visitors to the Site, the URL that you just came from and where you next go to, and your computer browser information. This data may help us determine better customer service and Site needs. CloudWork may use this data with third parties in aggregate form, but not in a manner that would identify you personally. We may provide aggregate information, not information about you personally, to our partners about how our users, collectively, use our Site and Service. We may store a 24 hours log of your data for troubleshooting reasons. If an error occurs the log may be stored for longer period of time to help us troubleshoot user issues.

## External Links

This Privacy Policy applies to the CloudWork Site and Service only. We do not exercise control over any sites that you may visit from a link on our Site. These other sites may place their own cookies or other files on your computer, collect data or solicit personal information from you.

## User Consent

By sending your personal data, you declare to have read and accepted the terms of this Policy. Without prejudice to the generality of the foregoing, you expressly and unequivocally consent to:

  * the collection and processing of your professional contact details by CloudWork in accordance with the indicated purposes established by CloudWork and this Policy;
  * the processing of your data outside the European Economic Area by third party data processors (e.g. for the purpose of providing professional services to us such as hosting or database management services); and
  * the reception of commercial e-mails from CloudWork, in accordance with the applicable laws on Information Society Services and Electronic Commerce.
  * the communication of the data to other site Users outside the European Economic Area at the request of the User.

Your consent to personal data collection and processing may be revoked in accordance to Sections 6 and 11 of Spanish Data Protection Basic Law 15/1999.

## Data Disclosure

CloudWork warrants that it treats your personal data with strict confidentiality in accordance with applicable law. However there are some situations in which CloudWork shall disclose any personally identifiable and/or non personally identifiable information about you or your use of our Site and Service, in compliance with a legal obligation or in order to correctly deliver its services or perform other obligations in accordance to the applicable regulations and rules set forth in the Terms of Use of the Site and Service.

In relation to international disclosures, Users expressly accept that we may disclose or internationally transfer your data to other Users and third parties that are located outside the European Union. This international disclosure or transfer will only be performed for the sole purposes stated under these Terms and Conditions.

We may use third party service providers to facilitate or outsource some aspects of our business and therefore we may provide some of your personal information directly to these service providers. These service providers are subject to legal restrictions that prohibit their use of the information we provide them for any other purpose except to facilitate the specific outsourced related operation. We may share our data, including personal information about you with our partners and joint ventures in furtherance of our business. To the extent that these entities have access to your information, they will treat it at least as protectively as they treat information they obtain from their other users. Our partners and joint ventures should follow privacy practices no less protective of all users than our practices described in this document, to the extent allowed by applicable law. In some cases, we may choose to buy or sell assets. In these types of transactions, customer information is typically one of the business assets that is transferred. Moreover, if CloudWork, or substantially all of its assets, were acquired, or in the unlikely event that CloudWork goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, customer information would be one of the assets that may be transferred to or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of CloudWork may continue to use your personal information as set forth in this policy.

## Data Security

We have implemented reasonable technical and organizational measures set forth to preserve your personal information protected from unauthorized use or access and from being altered, lost or misused, taking into account the technological state of art, the features of the information stored and the risks to which information is exposed, in accordance with Royal Decree 1720/2007 implementing the Spanish Data Protection Law 15/1999.

We use industry-standard Secure Socket Layer (SSL) software to protect the security of your personal information during transmission, which encrypts all of the information you input. All personal information collected from other services that you provide through the use of the Service is stored securely. Only employees who need personal information to perform a specific job (i.e. customer services) are granted access to it.

However, due to the nature of the information and related technology, we cannot ensure or guarantee the security of your personal information and expressly disclaims any such obligation. If we learn of a security breach, then we will attempt to notify you electronically so that you can take appropriate steps.

## Usernames and Passwords

You need to protect against unauthorized access to your usernames and passwords. You are responsible for all actions taken with your User ID and password. Therefore we recommend that you do not disclose your password to any third parties. If you choose to share your User ID and password or your personal information with third parties, you are responsible for all actions taken with your account and therefore you should review that third party's privacy policy. If your password has been compromised for any reason, you should immediately change your password.

## Authentication Information

When you use CloudWork to make connections between various web services we need authentication information to enable those connections on your behalf. Once you provide authentication details CloudWork will retrieve and modify data providing from these web services on your behalf, but only in a manner that is specified by the Service you choose.

## Cookies

When you visit the Site, we may send one or more "cookies" to your computer through your web browser. Any use of cookies will be solely for the purposes of improving the quality of access to the Site by storing user preferences, and tracking user trends, such as how people use the Site, and their Site access preferences. We use cookies to allow you to enter your login information less frequently. Such cookies do not collect personal information, and we do not combine information collected through cookies with other personal information to tell what your username or e-mail address is or us who you are.

You are always free to decline our cookies, although in that case you will not be able to use core features of the Site and Service such as registration, login, access to integrations and more. We recommend that you leave the cookies activated because deleting cookies will reduce the functionality of CloudWork. We do not control the use of cookies by third parties.

## Use of User Data

As a registered user of the Site and the Service, you have supplied your email address, and we may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with our newest work. If you contact CloudWork (i.e. for support, feedback, feature request…) we reserve the right to publish it in order to help clarify or respond to your request or to help support other users.

Any User of the Site who is provided with personal data of other Users expressly agrees to:

  * process and use the data in accordance with the terms set forth herein and only for the explicit purposes of the Service, or otherwise with the consent of the User.
  * not to transfer any personal data relating to any individual that has not been expressly authorized by that person or this Policy.
  * protect the confidentiality of any accessible personal data and avoiding access by any unauthorized third person.
  * inform CloudWork within 24 hours about any problem arisen in relation with user data management.

The receiving User agrees to be responsible for any illegal use by them of the Site Users’ data. In regard to this clause, illegal use is to be construed to include any use contrary to the applicable data protection laws and/or in violation this Privacy Policy.

## Commerical Communications

By sending your data to CloudWork during registration, you expressly consent to receive commercial communications regarding the subject matter of the Site and Service in accordance to section 22 of Spanish law on Ecommerce (Law 34/2002). These commercial communications, including alerts, notices, newsletters, offers and promotions will be always sent by CloudWork.

If you do not wish to receive information from this Site you can expressly opt out by sending a notification to [optout@cloudwork.com](mailto:optout@cloudwork.com).

## Privacy Policy Changes

We may amend this privacy policy as required to adapt it to future legislative or case law developments, and this will be reflected by the “effective date” below. If we make any substantive changes in our treatment of information collected at this Site and Service, we will notify you by posting a clear notice of these changes on our Site and in this privacy policy. Your continued use of the Site and Service constitutes your agreement to this Privacy Policy and any future revisions. This Privacy Policy was last modified on January 28th, 2013

## Applicable Law

Unless a specific local regulation sets forth to the contrary, the Privacy Policy and the remainder of the Terms of Use of the Site and Service are governed by Spanish law.

## Contact Us

If users experience problems while exercising their online rights or if they have doubts or questions related to our Privacy Policy or Terms of Use they can contact us directly at: CloudWork., Diagonal 622, 7.2, 08021 Barcelona, Spain. Or through our e-mail: [legal@cloudwork.com](mailto:legal@cloudwork.com) indicating the reference matter.
